Walter Snow Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Walter Snow Papers.
undated, 1926-1973.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Snow, Walter.
7.5 linear feet
The papers include the correspondence, short stories, journalistic articles, correspondence, poems, novels, and plays of journalist, essayist, novelist and pulp fiction writer, Walter Snow.
MSS19750005
Biography
Walter Snow (1905-1973) was a pulp fiction writer, mystery novelist, socialist essayist, and newspaper journalist. He spent much of his early life attempting to fulfill his ambition of becoming a great proletariat writer. Snow became, instead, a successful journalist, a prolific writer of adventure and detective stories, and of realistic short fiction. Snow's writing style is characterized by his ability to bring his characters to life. When writing as a journalist, Snow utilized his ability as a detailed storyteller to illuminate the nature of the person he was writing about. Snow was alternately published under the pen names Chris Graham in his early pulp fiction writings as well as Robert Clark in his socialist essays.
Snow was born on 19 February 1905 in Gardner, Massachusetts, to Robert O. Snow and Emma Groszmann. Growing up, Snow attended schools in both Connecticut and Massachusetts. He graduated from South Hadley, Massachusetts High School in 1921. Snow was part of the fifth generation of his family to work as a laborer. Snow began working in the American Thread Company textile mills of South Hadley, Massachusetts, during the summer of 1920. Following high school, Snow worked in Willimantic, Connecticut, at the American Thread Company. From 1921 until 1924, Snow held a variety of positions such as jag boy, thread carrier, Order's Department "chaser", and as Works Department timekeeper and clerk. He was laid off during the retrenchment just before the six-month 1925 strike.
Snow witnessed strikers evicted from their company-owned housing; left to freeze on the roadside of Route 6 during the winter months. National Guardsmen called in and compensated by the mill owners, treated strikers in some cases violently. With the help of a loosely formed union, strikers were able to return to their homes and avoid starvation and death. By working in the mills and witnessing the mistreatment of workers like him, Snow experienced inadequate working conditions, which inspired his social activism and fostered his socialist viewpoints. Following his time working at American Thread, Snow moved to New York City. Upon arriving in New York, he went to work as a stagehand and scene painter for the Providence Playhouse in Greenwich Village under Eugene O'Neil. He also married his first wife, Edith, in 1926.
During the 1920s-1930s, Snow lived primarily in New York City. From 1925-1930, Snow was a police reporter and rewrite man. Throughout the 1930s, Snow worked primarily as a reporter for The Home News reviewing films and plays. Associated with the New York Rebel Poets, Snow began writing prose and poetry for magazines following the Sacco-Vanzetti executions in 1927. He met and worked with contemporaries such as Jack Conroy and Philip Rahv, who advocated workers rights and socialist attitudes. From the late 1920s to the early 1930s, Snow was actively involved with the Communist party and John Reed Club. In the middle of the 1930s, Snow ceased active involvement in the party and club, but continued his literary involvement in the movement. With Conroy, Snow served as a co-editor of The Anvil until it merged with Rahv's Partisan Review. His articles were also featured in New Masses and International Literature. He served as a volunteer organizer for the Newspaper Guild and the American Labor party toward the end of the 1930s. During this period, Snow moved from New York City to Chaplin, CT, then Willimantic, CT, and by the end of the 1930s was again living in New York City.
Despite numerous attempts to make their marriage a success, Snow was no longer married to his wife Edith by the beginning of World War II. Snow served in the military in Georgia during World War II in 1943. It is unclear how long he was active in the armed forces. Snow wrote sparingly during this decade.
Following World War II, Snow left New York and returned to Connecticut. Snow eventually met Flora Huffman whom he would marry and remain married to for the duration of his life. He had a daughter and a stepson, Maurice Isserman. In the early the 1950s, Snow was primarily writing for the pulp fiction market. Snow was published in pulp fiction magazines including Gang World, Mike Shayne Mystery Magazine, Short Stories, and Suspect Detective Stories. Seven of his mysteries were anthologized in six hardcover and three paperback books including 1951's 20 Great Tales of Murder, and 1970's With Malice Towards All. Snow wrote two mystery novels, 1952's The Golden Nightmare, and 1972's The Gauguin Murders (unpublished). His final work The Glory and the Shame, a collection of his poetry from 1927-1972, was published in 1973.
While never abandoning writing fiction, by the middle of the 1960s, Snow was making a transition back to journalism. Snow started working as a free-lance correspondent for the Willimantic Chronicle. He continued to work in a variety of positions for the Chronicle until his retirement in 1973. Snow was a correspondent who covered the Connecticut General Assembly, a part-time reviewer of plays at the University of Connecticut, as well as the paper's editor, a position that his father once held. Snow was a member of the Laurel Club, which is an organization of legislative correspondents. He was known as a conscientious newsman who was deeply interested in civil rights and the human condition.
Walter Snow died in 1973.
Scope and Content
The Walter Snow Papers contain the surviving manuscripts of Walter Snow (both published and unpublished). These works include short stories, journalistic articles, correspondence, poems, novels, and plays. Most of Snow's surviving correspondence relates to his attempts to get his works published. The bulk of the remaining correspondence contains information about Snow's involvement with The Anvil, which he edited with Jack Conroy and others in the early 1930s. The collection also contains notes, outlines, and print ephemera. This collection contains extensive materials prior to 1940 and for the period from 1956 until his death in 1973. In the early 1930s, Snow began a project on the textile industry in southern New England. While he never finished the novel, the notes on the textile mills may be of use to scholars interested in textile mills during this period.
Arrangement
Series I: Biographical Material ( undated, 1930-1973 ) includes portions of Snow's journal, notebook, and an extensive collection of biographical information that Snow gave to editors. Obituaries and articles written about Snow are also contained in this series. Finally, this series contains information about the merger of The Anvil and Partisan Review from Snow and Jack Conroy.
Series II: Correspondence ( undated, 1927-1930, 1971-1973 ) contains surviving correspondence not filed with published works. The bulk of the correspondence was with fellow writers and/or editors including Hayden Carruth, Jack Conroy, Marvin Malone, Seymour Ponds, and A.H. Sinks.
Series III: Journalistic Work ( undated, 1927-1941, 1959-1973 ) is divided into manuscripts and clippings of published works. The bulk of the manuscripts are articles submitted to publications such as The Anvil. The earliest clippings are film and drama reviews for The Home News. Starting in 1959, Snow returned to journalism. He wrote reviews of plays at the University of Connecticut as well as travel pieces, which are also evidenced in the clippings.
Series IV: Fictional Works ( undated, 1928-1973 ) encompasses primarily typed manuscripts of Snow's novels, plays, and poetry. It includes not only the written works, but also any notes and correspondence relevant to Snow's writings.
Series V: Short Fiction ( undated, 1928-1933, 1941-1970 ) includes typed manuscripts of Snow's short stories with notes and correspondence. Writing for mostly pulp publications, short stories are the most extensive genre of fiction in which Snow wrote. The items are order chronologically by place of residence as indicated by Snow and then by date.
Series V: Notes ( undated, 1926-1972 ) contains outlines and notes by Snow for potential works. It also contains some analysis of works of fiction by other writers.
Series VI: Ephemera ( undated, circa 1930-1973 ) includes a wide variety of materials. The bulk of this series contains newspaper clippings written by others. It also contains typed manuscripts of three stories for The Anvil by other authors that were possibly edited by Snow.
Series VII: Pulp Literature ( 1931-1968 ) contains published copies of Snow's work. These items are very fragile and access is at the Curator's discretion.
Eric Carlson, a friend of Snow and professor of English at the University of Connecticut, organized the papers originally. In 1981, Ellen E. Embardo reorganized pieces of the collection and created the original finding aid.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to literature. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Bibliography
Exiles from a Future Time. Alan M. Wald; 2002.
Worker-writer in Americirca Douglas Wixson; 1999.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Snow, Walter.
Places:
Connecticut--Newspapers, periodicals, and journalism.; Willimantic (Conn.)--Newspapers, periodicals, and journalism.; New York (N.Y.)--Newspapers, periodicals, and journalism.; Connecticut--Cultral affairs--Literature.; New York (N.Y.)--Cultral affairs--Literature.; Coventry (Conn.)--Cultral affairs--Literature.
Organizations:
Subjects:
American literature--New York (State)--New York.; American literature--Connecticut.; American literature--20th century.; American poetry--20th century.; American poetry--Connecticut.; American poetry--New York (State)--New York.; Rebel poets--New York (State)--New York.; Journalism--Editing.; American newspapers--Connecticut.; American newspapers--New York (State)--New York.; American periodicals--New York (State)--New York.; American newspapers--Illinois.; Social movements--United States.; Detective and mystery stories, American.; Radicalism--United States.; Poets, American--Political activity.; Authors, American--Political activity.; Communism--Periodicals.; Communism--Newspapers.; Communism--United States.; Socialism--United States.; Labor unions--Press employees--United States.; Labor unions--Organizaing.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Notebooks.; Publications.; Photographs.; Manuscripts.; Typescripts.; Photocopies.; Notes.; Books.; Obituaries.; Poems.; Newspapers.; Pulp literature.; Fiction.; Scripts.; Periodicals.
Occupations:
Journalists--Connecticut.; Journalists--New York (State)--New York.; Authors--American.; Poets--American.; Periodical editors--New York (State)--New York.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection with the exception of Series VII: Pulp Literature. Access to this series is at the Curator's discretion.
Acquisition Information
The materials in this collection were donated shortly after Walter Snow's death in 1973.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series I: Biographical Material, undated, 1930-1973
  - Biographical Information (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Biographical summaries for editors and correspondents (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Notes and papers related to first wife, Edna (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Notes written about his family (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Journal (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Notebook (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Clippings about Snow (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Clippings about second wife Flora or stepson Maurice Isserman (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Information about the merger of The Anvil and The Partisans Review with "That Literary Shotgun Marriage" submitted by Walt Snow, 1973 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
- Series II: Correspondence, undated, 1927-1930, 1971-1973
  - Ackerson, Jack, 1932-1933 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Axelrod, T., 1932-1933 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Bates, Harry, 1929 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Beckwith, Russell, 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Blunder, Edmund, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Brown, Haywood, 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Katherine (RKO Radio Pictures), 1932-1933 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Burns, 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Cacciatore, Vera, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - Carmon, Walt, 1930-1933 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Carruth, Hayden, 1971-1972 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
  - Carruth, Hayden, 1973 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
  - Cave, Hugh, 1932-1933 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
  - Chadwick, Paul, 1963 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
  - Chalmers, [Mr.], 1932 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
  - Clements, A.E., 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
  - Colvin, Ken C., undated, 1927-1929 (Box 1:, Folder 26)
  - Colyer, Noel [Dr. and Mrs.], 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 27)
  - Conklin, Margaret (Macmillan Co.), 1933 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
  - Conroy, Jack, 1930-1933 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
  - Conroy, Jack, 1969-1973 (Box 1:, Folder 30)
  - Cromie, Bob, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 31)
  - Gordon, David (Daily World), 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 32)
  - Gunn, Harold, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 33)
  - Hagglund, Ben C., 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 34)
  - Harrison, Charles Yale, 1930 (Box 2:, Folder 35)
  - Hicks, Granville, 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 36)
  - Hilburn, 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 37)
  - Houghton, Arthur [Mrs.], 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 38)
  - Isserman, Maurice (stepson), 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 39)
  - Jarraboe, George, 1932-1933 (Box 2:, Folder 40)
  - James, Kelly, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 41)
  - Kalar, John, 1932 (Box 2:, Folder 42)
  - Koheuhausin, Louise (cousin), 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 43)
  - Lewis, C. Day, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 44)
  - Linden, [Dr.], 1962 (Box 2:, Folder 45)
  - Malone, Marvin (Wormwood Review), 1971-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 46)
  - Massur, Hal (Mystery Writers of America), 1970-1971 (Box 2:, Folder 47)
  - Maybocci, Antoinette, 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 48)
  - Medary, Majorie, 1969, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 49)
  - Moravsky, Maria, 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 50)
  - Moroze, Lewis (American Dialog), 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 51)
  - Peizner, J. (New Masses), 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 52)
  - Pollett, Joseph, 1930 (Box 2:, Folder 53)
  - Ponds, Seymour, 1927-1931 (Box 2:, Folder 54)
  - Publicity Department, Harcourt, Brace & Co., 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 55)
  - Publicity Department, Houghton Mifflin Co., 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 56)
  - Rich, H. Thompson, 1929 (Box 2:, Folder 57)
  - Roberts, J., 1968 (Box 2:, Folder 58)
  - Rogers, John C., 1932-1933 (Box 2:, Folder 59)
  - "Salty Bill" (Doubleday), 1928 (Box 2:, Folder 60)
  - Singleton, Nina, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
  - Sinks, A.H., 1929, 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 62)
  - Smith, Bernard, 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 63)
  - "Smith, Harry" (Sidney Bernard ed. Newsletter on the state of culture), 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
  - Spector, Herman (Dynamo), 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 65)
  - Spier, Lewis, 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 66)
  - Sternberg, Ann, 1968 (Box 2:, Folder 67)
  - Stevens, Karey, undated (Box 2:, Folder 68)
  - Vassallo, Carol, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 69)
  - Wagner, Charles A. (Poetry Society of America), 1972-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 70)
  - Walker, V.B., 1929 (Box 2:, Folder 71)
  - Weiss, H.G., 1933 (Box 2:, Folder 72)
  - Wellington, Grace, 1932-1933 (Box 2:, Folder 73)
  - White, Gail, 1973 (Box 2:, Folder 74)
  - Wilsack, John, 1932-1933 (Box 2:, Folder 75)
  - Unidentified Correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 2:, Folder 76)
  - Unidentified Correspondence, undated, 1971-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 77)
- Series III: Journalistic Works, undated, 1927-1941, 1959-1973
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts, undated, 1930-1973
    - "Fiction Crime Slave", 1930 (Box 3:, Folder 78)
    - "Red Lights on Grub Street", 1931 (Box 3:, Folder 79)
    - "The Flaming Torch Messiahs Squabble", 1932 (Box 3:, Folder 80)
    - Book Reviews for The Anvil, 1932-1933 (Box 3:, Folder 81)
      - Review of Red Songbook, 1932 December 10
      - "From Mountaineers to Revolutionists" (Review of To Make My Bread), 1933 January 16
      - "The Heroes of Blup" (Review of The Bulpington of Blup), 1933 June 6
    - "Underdogs and Inflation", 1933 (Box 3:, Folder 82)
    - "Grub-street--1933" (Box 3:, Folder 83)
    - "The Renaissance of American Proletarian Literature", 1934 (Box 3:, Folder 84)
    - Articles published in New Masses, 1934 (Box 3:, Folder 85)
      - "Flying Squadron Crash Through", 1934 September 19
      - "45,000 Strikers Fight Rhode Island Terror", 1934 September 25
    - "For Russell Beckwith", circa 1930s (Box 3:, Folder 86)
    - "Grub Street in Hooverland", circa 1930s (Box 3:, Folder 87)
    - Max Eastman's Marx and Lenin", circa 1930s (Box 3:, Folder 88)
    - "Sweatshop Paradise Guaranteed", circa 1930s (Box 3:, Folder 89)
    - "The Anvil and Proletarian Short Story", circa 1930s (Box 3:, Folder 90)
    - Letters for New Masses Reader's Forum", 1941 May 19, 1941 May 31 (Box 3:, Folder 91)
    - "Readers Report on Manhattan Homestead: Freelance Living by Daniel and Marion Whedon", 1941 October 11, 1941 November 15 (Box 3:, Folder 92)
    - Letter to the Editor of New York Herald Tribune, "Answer to Toni Stopler and Other Detractors of Pearl Buck and Walter Lippmann,", 1942 February 28 (Box 3:, Folder 93)
    - Original Manuscript of the review of Watch on the Rhine for The Home News, 1943 (Box 3:, Folder 94)
    - Original Manuscript of "Liberty Goes to the Movies" (Review of Jane Eyre), 1944 February 11 (Box 3:, Folder 95)
    - "Who Says Short Story is Dead!" for Writer's Digest, 1965 December 8 (Box 3:, Folder 96)
    - Potential article on Marcia Savella, 1969 May 9 (Box 3:, Folder 97)
    - "Dramatic Monologue on Hawthorne's Problems", (unpublished), 1971 September 29 (Box 3:, Folder 98)
    - Auto-biographical article/publicity piece, 1973 January 22 (Box 3:, Folder 99)
    - "Poetic Prostitutes of the Spooks" submitted to Daily World, 1973 March 31 (Box 3:, Folder 100)
    - Book review of Residence on Earth by Paul Neruda and Letter to the Editor about Neruda submitted to New York Times, circa 1973 June 5 (Box 3:, Folder 101)
    - "Atheism: A Partial Foundation for Proletarian Poetry", undated (Box 3:, Folder 102)
  - Subseries B: Clippings, undated, 1927-1971
    - Articles printed in The Daily Worker, 1927-1928 (Box 16:)
      - "A New American Epic", undated
      - "Mrs. Rose Sacco: A Fighter", 1927 August 31
      - "Karlin Disobeys Orders", 1927 September 1
      - "Leary and Labor", 1927 September 3
      - "Reading 'Between the Lines' about Paris", 1927 September 20
      - "'Legion For Peace,' But Jingoes Wives Attack Pacificism", 1927 September 23
      - "Disillusions and Dollars", 1927 November 5
      - "Short Stories in a Novel", 1927 November 11
      - "Minor Music", 1928 January 2
      - "'Defeat and Darkness' Juggler's Kiss", 1928 January 24
      - "Dunn's Company Unions Analyzed", 1928 February 25
    - Letter to the Editor Willimantic Chronicle re U.S. Senator Hiram Bingham, 1932 October 26 (Box 3:, Folder 103)
    - "Stories, Poems in "Anvil" Reflect Workers' Struggles"(Review of The Anvil in The Daily Worker by Isidor Schneider), 1934 (Box 3:, Folder 104)
    - The Home News, 1934-1937 (Box 3:, Folder 105)
      - Brain Sweat, 1934 April 6
      - "Bronx Photographer Records Dominant Spirit of Dynamic Mussolini in 45-Minute Audience", 1935 October 6
      - The Case of Philip Lawrence, 1937 June 9
      - "'Gus' Smith, Veteran of Stage and Screen Presides Over Harlem's Famed WPA Actors", 1937 June 20
      - Theatre Notes and Riding on Air, 1937 June 28
      - "Harlem Actors Fear WPA Retrenchment May Mean End of Federal Negro Theatre", 1937 July 4
      - "Anita Bush's Campaign for Colored Theatre Recalled by Featured Role in WPA Musical", 1937 August 22
    - The Home News, 1937-1938 (Box 3:, Folder 106)
      - Horse Play, 1937 August 28
      - "Theatre Notes", 1937 August 30
      - Moon of the Caribees, 1937 October 30
      - Mississippi Rainbow, 1938 March 5
    - The Home News, 1939-1940 (Box 3:, Folder 107)
      - Wuthering Heights, 1939 April 15
      - Wuthering Heights, 1939 April 28
      - Morning Star, 1940 April 17
      - Heavenly Express, 1940 April 19
      - There Shall Be No Night, 1940 April 30
    - Sunday Workers Progressive Weekly, 1939 (Box 3:, Folder 108)
      - "Cuba Drafts Her Bill of Rights", 1939 September 17
      - "From the Rich Red Soil of Cube", 1939 September 30
      - "The Man of September Fourth", 1939 October 1
    - The Home News, 1940-1942 (Box 3:, Folder 109)
      - Journey to Jerusalem, 1940 October 7
      - Arsenic and Old Lace January 11, 1941, 1941 January 11
      - Sea Wolf March 22, 1941, 1941 March 22
      - Maltese Falcon, 1941 October 4
      - Banjo Eyes, 1941 December 26
      - Louisiana Purchase, 1942 January 2
      - The Rivals, 1942 January 15
      - Hedda Gabler, 1942 January 30
    - The Home News, 1942 (Box 3:, Folder 110)
      - The Moon is Down, 1942 April 8
      - Remember Pearl Harbor June 4, 1942, 1942 June 4
      - Laugh, Town, Laugh, 1942 June 23
      - Are Husbands Necessary, 1942 July 9
      - Spy Ship, 1942 July 13
      - Brooklyn U.S.A., 1942 July 15
      - The Merry Widow, 1942 July 16
      - Priorities on Parade, 1942 July 23
      - Crossroads, 1942 July 24
      - The Glass Key, 1942 September 15
      - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1942 November 19
      - The Great Big Doorstep, 1942 Novebmer 27
      - Random Harvest, 1942 December 18
      - The Three Sisters, 1942 December 19
    - Tennessee Johnson (film review), Christian Science Monitor, 1943 January 13 (Box 3:, Folder 111)
    - The Home News, 1943-1944 (Box 3:, Folder 112)
      - "War Grimness Stressed by Bronx Flier Who Has Seen Friends 'Go Up in Flames'", 1943 October 8
      - "Major H.L. Schwamm, World War Veteran, Is Elected President Of National Bronx Bank", 1944 March 31
    - The Home News, undated (Box 3:, Folder 113)
      - "'Oh Johnny' Need Not Pay 'Oh Honey' of Yesterday"
      - "Waves Will Wear Winning Warm Weather Washables"
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1959-1965 (Box 3:, Folder 114)
      - "Time of Cuckoo Climaxes Uconn Summer Play Fete", 1959 August 5
      - "Gigi Proves Charming At New Studio Theatre", 1959 December 5
      - "Thousand Clowns Rings With Laughter at Uconn", 1964 July 8
      - "Tunnel of Love Is Barrel of Laughs", 1964 August 5
      - "Vote Is Three To One For King of Hearts,", 1964 August 12
      - "Merchant of Venice Again Colorful and Controversial", 1964 December 8
      - "Albatross Satirizes TV at Uconn's Playhouse", 1965 July 7
      - "'Black Irish Humor' Adds Bite to 'Hostage' Hijinks", 1965 August 15
      - "A Man for All Seasons Proves Exciting on UC Stage", 1965 October 26
      - "Cocktail Party Sparkles; Uconn Theatre at Its Best", 1965 December 4
    - Letter to the Editor Hartford Courant "The Infidels", 1962 July 9 (Box 3:, Folder 115)
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1965-1966 (Box 3:, Folder 116)
      - "Sheridan's 1779 Burlesque Is Timely, Hilarious at UC", 1965 December 15
      - "Braggart Soldier Is Rowdy, Pagan, Modern", 1966 February 26
      - "Braggart Soldier Is Rowdy, Pagan, Modern", 1966 March 2
      - "Three Sisters Evokes 'Twilight Magic' at UC", 1966 April 18
      - "Uconn's The Physicists Is Nuclear Age Satire", 1966 May 4
      - "Moliere's Doctor Is Amusing Spoof at UC", 1966 May 14
      - "UC's Carnival Called Gala Musical and Circus", 1966 May 18
      - "Virginia Woolf Is Exciting and Savage at UC Nutmeg", 1966 June 29
      - "Tender Trap Is Laugh Riot at UC's Nutmeg Playhouse", 1966 July 6
      - "U.S.A. Evokes Nostalgia At UC's Nutmeg Playhouse", 1966 July 13